if she's going to find you know a Justin
Bieber like I my example last time you
were on you know someone you know that's
richer or more powerful because I'm sure
that you know a lot of guys will come in
your life and try to you know and they
don't care whether you have a boyfriend
or not they're still going to try to
pursue you so you have to you know you
have to be in that situ you have to like
as a man you'd have to be really really
really
secure yeah I would say that he
definitely is he's very very Ure he has
his moments where he acts a little crazy
but I think we all do yeah I'm sure and
you have a crazy lifestyle so when it
when it came to like how are you growing
up like how like as a kid um I'm sure
because you're really talented and I and
I think you're intelligent you know I I
think that you you're you're highly
intelligent uh how how how were you
treated as a kid in in school that's
interesting I was uh I was a nerd I was
a
geek um I didn't have a whole lot of
friends um when I took ballet there was
a point where I had to leave ballet and
I'm not really sure why and it was at
that point like I just changed as a
person um I ended up getting into a
friendship that just probably wasn't the
best friendship for me at that time um
we are no longer friends I really
appreciate this person and she was
really really close to me but we made
wrong decisions together and we got
ourselves into some trouble here and
there so I think I was I was almost like
retaliating against my parents for
attention right and then by High School
um I gotten into so much trouble that I
think that kids didn't really want to be
my friend so I started hanging out with
band and
choir kids and that was when I I decided
like hey I should focus on like my
artistic abilities because I I have a
bit of talent and it's going to keep me
out of trouble so I did that and then I
mean After High School I lost my father
got into more trouble I mean my life has
been quite an interesting story and
that's why I'm going to write a book I
have been writing the book and um how
everything just kind of came together
for my life
life and that kind of stuff but um for
the most part I was picked on and teased
um there were days I ate I ate my lunch
in the bathroom to avoid
people um whoa that's crazy yeah I
remember a girl uh throwing apples at me
and I get picked on I still have some of
my high school bullies still picking on
me they still roast me online but not at
this point now I kind of look at it as
you're still like this like you haven't
moved on you haven't grown up you
haven't done anything you're still
picking on me okay I'm flattered yeah
you know when I was on YouTube um I used
to get the n-word a lot and you know I
got a lot of VD like a lot of hits and
stuff like that and and I realized that
you know when you when they made me
partner and I started making money off
every every video I was like hate on
hate on give me the hate you know
because the hate kind of gave me uh you
know it made me a lot of money you know
for just Lage schol honestly like I mean
for the people that I don't really like
I don't really have an opinion
on like it's not even that I don't like
you it's just like I don't have an
opinion on you're you're living your own
life you're having your own lifestyle
you're doing what you do I don't even
know what your job is and that's how
much I know about you but for me it's a
little bit different when they hate on
me it's because they see me doing things
they see me making moves and they want
to say something and I don't know I I
just let them do that at this point
there are times where I get involved
online and I
start being Saucy back
but um I think I do that for to the
hustle Zone this is Ryan Perez uh this
is volume two hustle Zone
2.0 so um I super excited so how are you
guys doing today who is in the house
oops not it's not the great debate today
okay
so um let me just see who's in the house
oh we got Richard in the house we got
Patrick we got Mark Duncan um how are
you folks doing
today um I'm so happy to uh do this
again uh so yeah folks you know we're
getting ready to launch this magazine
pretty soon so I am super duper duper um
excited for all What's transpiring um we
have now closed the the submission for
uh writers uh we have over 20 um active
writers that will be writing on the
hustle Zone and you know people are just
enth thrilled because they're finally
you know there's going to be a place
where people will have their voice you
know without it being overly spamed
Etc you know we really want to instead
of talking about entrepreneurialism as
that lifestyle uh because that's a you
know it's more like a I I would say it's
more like a Salesman lifestyle it's like
make a lot of money spend a lot of money
look great have you know nice cars and
stuff like that but you know um I I want
to capture the full lifestyle of the the
the the the the entrepreneur you know
the culture around just waking up early
in the morning go to bed late at night
um you know just your interactions with
family and whatnot and it kind of plays
with what the hustle Zone has always
been about um it has always been about
um you know the person's story and now
we're this website's going to be a
collection of stories uh and and I would
like to talk to you guys like I I I put
all the the links just out of uh um you
know feedback from last shows like we
people couldn't find the links to a lot
of the stuff so you guys if to support
the hustle Zone I wouldn't be able to do
it without your support uh you can
definitely donate um to the hustle Zone
I put my PayPal link up there also you
can like our our Facebook page um you
can add yourself to our group so you can
keep informed when there are events
coming on with the hustle Zone um you
can follow us on Twitter uh and um and
then also if you want to purchase hustle
Zone clothing uh I know that I could not
pronounce the link for the life of me
not pronounce but just did out it's like
get that t with hyphens in the middle
forward SLB tie half hyphen all that
stuff so I purchased the domain hustle
zone. clo so if you just click that it
goes directly to our clothes so um you
can click that and it just leads you
there so all the links are in the um in
the uh the link and then we got Jason
Daniels in the house so uh we got
crystal in the house uh um and folks I'm
like I'm asking you guys to now that we
are stepping up the game folks like and
share like and share like and share like
and share like you know show people that
this is this is valuable if you guys see
great quality we have great quality
guests and and the mic is good the the
visuals are good share like and share
you know share that with other people so
that they can see you know uh the
beautiful things that we're doing thank
you Daniel for sharing I really
appreciate that so we got Crystal Jones
and and CST Jones she she is she she
helped me put a lot of this stuff
together behind the scenes so I want to
give a special shout out to her uh Jason
Daniels uh we we had a a chat um a few
days ago and just loved what I see or
what I saw and and you know he's an
excellent person so you're going to see
more of Jason more of Crystal uh and
you're going to see more of this guest
that we have uh today now um I met this
guest uh at on the set of Fargo cuz I
was doing extra work because being an
entrepreneur sometimes can get very
boring especially in my life and
um uh when I met this guest I was I was
just hopping tables I seen two beautiful
ladies uh sitting at the table and they
were talking to themselves and then I
was sitting in front of some other
people I'm like you know what I'm just
going to go and talk to the beautiful
ladies I'm just going to just skip over
here so uh so it's exactly what I did
and um and then I met uh uh I met this
guess and you know I was I was just kind
of in the mode cuz I was working and and
and whatnot working on the set of Fargo
trying to get some stuff done uh for a
client and
um I
uh h i I guess I don't know how the
conversation started I guess her friend
asked me some random question I didn't
know I was like what the what what is
she asking me uh and then uh and she was
telling me what she does and then uh her
um uh and they're both two cool people
um and then this guest was like I'm a
writer I'm a writer I'm a writer you
know like she was Raising her hand like
you know and she was just letting me
know like she wanted me to know that she
was a she was a star as well she's like
I'm on
Instagram I got like
I got I got like um you know like 60,000
followers or whatever it was I don't
remember the number and I was like
really she's so quiet what is she
talking about and then and then she
shows me her Instagram where I look it
up and legit she has those followers and
she's a upcoming actress she is a um
she's a bombshell she's beautiful uh and
so she's a model she's an actress and uh
she's a b she's a
businesswoman and at I believe she's 24
years old and hopefully you can correct
me but I mean she has so much talent you
know today I call her and you know she's
like in this site and the suite is all
nice and everything like just you know
she's living the boss's life so I am so
happy to bring to the show today Miss
Janine Marie so let me just get her mic
on how's it going
Janine I'm good thank you Ryan how are
you I'm doing good you're going to have
to speak up really loud because you're
really soft
spoken yeah I can be a little bit shy
okay so folks like I want you guys to
click the like button if you can hear
her her her audio because I just need to
know if it's on my end or if it's on on
on uh on her end so if you guys can send
me likes and let me see it let me see
it I'm not seeing any likes so I I think
uh and if you don't hear any likes send
an angry
face no don't send angry s send a send a
heart okay well nobody's responding so
that's okay I guess we'll just have to
go with what we go with all
right thank you so much for having me Ry
yeah so how how how's everything how's
how's life oh it's good I mean I'm here
in Vancouver right now um and I did a
fashion show or sorry fashion shoot
yesterday for my Instagram
page and then I'll be coming home
sometime this week I'm really excited to
come home because it turns out the
weather here is very very
gray is very gray yeah cuz Vancouver
life is is pretty like you know you have
the you know the weather is pretty
depressing it's not like Calgary where
it's you know nice and sunny but you
always yeah even on like snowy days in
Calgary it can be pretty sunshiny but
like for the most part in Vancouver it's
just gray I've seen the sun
once so what are you doing like tell me
a little bit about what you're doing in
uh
Vancouver well I was just G of here um
to visit my ads I saw her last evening
and then um I am here with um My
Bodyguard where just kind of hanging out
I did a shoot
yesterday and
um what else just mostly visiting
friends I like to go place to place for
for a little bit of a promotional
self-promotion kind of thing so that
other people find out who I am and I go
to different cities and hang out at cool
places oh so you're you're you're one of
those people you're the cool you're in
the cool crowd so um okay hold on I
wasn't always though you
w um let me ask you okay so you just
dropped that you you're hanging out with
a bodyguard like what do you like just
on Instagram like why you need a
bodyguard for like where where do The
Bodyguard I think I think he's more so
like a babysitter for me
why do you need a babysitter
stupid okay can you like dial that back
so like so you like so he's a babysitter
and he just makes sure that you're not
doing crazy stuff like uh like what
would be yeah basically he's just there
by my side making sure that I remain
poised and I'm not getting like stupid
drunk he doesn't drink he doesn't smoke
he's like a really good guy he just he
just stands there looks good
well I do my own
thing wow a really good
friend so okay pieces he likes to be
kept like I bet you he'll be mad that I
even talked about him because he doesn't
like to be like in the Limelight at all
he doesn't like to be in the Limelight
at all yeah so no I tell him he's got to
get used to it so tell me how did this
all start you know for you like what
what well before I before I go there
most people are going to you know get
mad at me if I don't ask this question
this has just been a routine of the
hustle Zone uh and for everyone knowing
what the hustle zone is is that we we we
don't like to talk about the glory so
much we like to talk about the story and
how people come come to be and how they
become entrepreneurs uh and um so Janine
what is your story and start from the
beginning like we got we got all day
well I was a young girl who was into
dancing I I danced um competitive dance
as a young girl and I got really really
into it um and so much into it that I
was telling my mom I'm gonna be a
superstar and she's like no you're
not and I'm like yes I am Mom I am going
to be a superstar so I started writing
my first book while I was in junior high
school um I honestly have no idea where
those pages are I think my mom has
them and then I was songwriting as well
and those songs sucked but I I always
kind of jumped into the Superstar mode
where I wanted to be able to have like a
really really large skill set from a
very young age so and then while I was
in high school um I was getting involved
more so in drama production
and um dance
Productions um and then by the end of
high school I had asked my dad if I
could get an agent and my dad took me to
my first
audition and my mom was not into the
idea
whatsoever um I don't know why that is
but we didn't we didn't really go into
it too much then
um then as the years went on I I moved
away from home and I kind of just worked
retail jobs because I've always been
into
fashion
um I ended up in a relationship at some
point or another that was took a took my
life for a turn for the
worst um I ended up homeless because of
this relationship ship because I wanted
to leave him so
badly um I was being
abused and it was not just emotional
abuse and financial abuse but it was
physical abuse as
well um so from that point I got out of
that
relationship and I
was I found myself into an
apartment but I couldn't afford the
apartment and the lifestyle that I
wanted and the lifestyle that I was was
used to with the jobs that I was having
at that time so again I ended up
homeless and this time it was a little
bit longer I was very very blessed that
I met some people who were willing to
help me they let me sleep on their
couches um they were complete strangers
to me they um became really good friends
one of them is Reverend Mike Cruz and
he's just like a really good friend to
me he's a local artist here in Calgary
he's a musici
I and um here in Calgary I'm in
Vancouver but he he ended up being like
a really really great guy unfortunately
he had to move out of his place because
the owner was looking to sell it and I
didn't know what I was going to do at
that point um and I just messaged a
friend of a friend and they put me in a
house and they took care of me for quite
some time um this boy changed my life
like
completely um unfortunately he was shot
and killed last
year and that's what kind of cuz he
believed in me so much that's what kind
of sparked my my
drive was that I have to do this for him
I have to do everything that I can do to
be successful because this boy who is a
complete stranger picked me up off of my
feet and believed in me so that was when
I kind of took took it seriously I
started messaging uh agencies and being
like please put me out there so I
started on doing background work on
settled
Fargo oh I skipped the part where I did
beauty pageants and car shows but I was
kind of already modeling at that point
um so I did a couple beauty pageants in
a car show I ended up winning Miss
driven last
year um which is for the driven car show
in
Calgary um and then from that point I
guess I just I started doing background
work and now I've been going I went to
an acting school in
Hollywood um taught by Adrian
rante which I don't know if anyone knows
it's like eston hul rooto dooso I don't
know the rest of his name but he's from
the Zach and Cody Sweet Life of Zach and
Cody show and he taught me some things
as an actress and I kind of just
realized at that moment when Hollywood
wanted to look at me and take me
seriously that I have this story and I
have this brand that I was kind of
building but now I have to take it
seriously I have to make it my career I
have to do everything for it
so that's what I'm doing now and since
I've started doing that I I think I'm
doing okay I think there's still a lot
of work to be done but I'm really happy
with the results I'm getting right now
that's that's that's amazing so you you
started off um homeless you know so
you've you've gone through so much and
then witnessing witnessing your not
witnessing that your friend got killed
but you know having someone that really
supported you and then have them killed
like how did that how did that make you
feel at the
time oh insane like it still makes me
really upset um I still have days where
I cry about it he was one of the best
friends I've ever had in my life and I
love him very very dearly and I believe
it was fate that uh brought him to my
life because uh his name was Louie but
for some reason we all called him Angelo
and in Italian Angelo means Angel so I
mean he's my
angel
wow
and when it came your mom wasn't really
happy with uh with you with you pursuing
this lifestyle and no not at all like I
don't we I don't know if we'll ever
really see eye to eye on it
you and and why why is
that
um I'm not really sure and maybe one day
I'll find
out could you could could it could it be
that
um could it be
that there's no sustainability in acting
in
modeling I think that she she was a
little bit fearful of like me not being
able
to uh Thrive MH um but I mean I'm just
kind of one of those people when I
believe in something and I want to do
something I just I have to do it and I
think that from a young age a lot of
people saw that in me but now it's kind
of like being taken a little bit more
seriously than it was in the past right
and how was your dad supporting you now
like with with all the stuff that you've
been doing and unfortunately my dad
passed away when I was 17 oh my
God yeah sorry to bring that up it's
okay I've experienced a lot of
heartbreak in my life but for that I am
thankful because I am a True Believer
without pain we would not appreciate
Beauty we would not appreciate the good
things that happened to us I think that
I would much rather
have like
be humbled that way I I'm not saying
that I'd much rather have him be gone
but I I I appreciate what it's taught me
in life right very much you know when I
uh when I met you um I can say that
uh when you oh there's like something
going on we got some technical
difficulties that's all good uh when
when I met you uh and when you were just
letting me know what you do
you were you know even though it was
very subtle it was pretty aggressive
it's like you know it's kind of like an
oxymoron it was like you really wanted
me to know and I you know and I thought
about that when I got home that's why
like I I like we I added you to Facebook
and then I messaged you and I'm like you
know she you just had something in you
that and I told you that you know off
camera it's like you know there's a fire
under you
right and I told that before you got
you're really you're like you know you
you know um you may be a pretty face but
you're you know when when you when
you're talking and stuff of that you're
very sharp and really focused on what
you want to attain and it seems that you
know you're not letting anyone get in
the way of that and maybe that has
something to do with the people that
you've lost in your life and again I my
condolences and then it also can be you
know because of your boyfriend and and
and can you expound upon that
relationship in a sense that you know
being an abusive relationship I think
that you know especially with someone um
you know as pretty as yourself you know
there's probably a lot of guys in your
life that are that are trying to control
your your your success and
control um who you are and and what what
what you want to do and I'm sure there's
a lot of guys that are
insecure when they're dating you that
they don't they're not securing
themselves to um to feel that you can
just live your life and post you know
pretty pictures on
Instagram um so yeah just to like expand
on that thought I'd say I'd have to
agree um a lot and I think that's why
that relationship ended up going in the
way that it went is because I think that
the men that are attracted to me think
that they can win me over but then they
get they get a sense of insecurity
around me and then they try to steal it
back somehow I'm not making excuses for
him wow had a we had a really bad
relationship um and it just took a turn
for the worse um but I'm very lucky that
I didn't
linger
because if I had I don't know where I'd
be now
and um I mean I'm just really blessed
that I pulled myself together and said
like I am not I'm not a person to stand
by this my dad taught me how I should be
raised and how I should be treated and
it is absolutely not this and I I knew
at one point in the relationship and I
can almost think of the day but I don't
want to get too specific but there was a
there was a moment where it was also it
was like almost like an ultimatum was
made and it was like it was him or
me and I just had to say you know what
no man who cares about me would ever
make me make that decision MH so from
that point I decided it was in it for me
and only me and I'm not only in it for
me anymore but yeah
I am at that point I had to
be yeah because I I I think most
entrepreneurs have that
um uh we when it comes to dating people
I think that you
know a lot of people don't want to be
second
place yeah they don't want to be put you
know because I've had that I've been in
that situation so you know it's been
really hard for me to to date in general
because you know my life me being a
single father um but also being an
entrepreneur my life comes first always
you know like in my world you know in my
little bubble that I've created for
myself because you know there's so many
people that I serve right there's so
many people in my life that um that I
have to do stuff for and and
unfortunately if I don't do it then I
get sued or whatever and I can't afford
to do that and then Al then at the same
time I'm an entrepreneur because I have
a beautiful son um and you know he does
crave my attention as well so a lot of
people have to be put on that back
burning so I guess I'm going to say that
um in your life you are like you know
you're you are a star you're upcoming
Star and you know not only that but you
are like you're worshiped on
Instagram I wouldn't say worship well I
mean like you know you got a lot of fans
right like that you know that just they
love the content that you produce so for
a guy it's gr pardon it's growing it's
growing so like when with the some of
the guys on there because you know like
you're you're
you're you like some pictures are risque
on your your your on your Instagram and
for a guy being your boyfriend how do
they deal with
that um I mean you'd have to ask my
boyfriend now I don't think that he has
too many issues with it um he he's just
very he's a very secure man um he
doesn't he he kind of like he feeds off
of it he's very happy with
uh I don't know that I have my own thing
going like he's very very supportive of
and I I'm very very lucky to have him
because because of that
reason because I up until him I never
found found a man that was secure enough
for me to be
me right because it's it's easy to be
jealous and be like you know every you
know to to think in the back of your
head like oh I wonder if she's cheating
I wonder if she's going to find you know
a Justin Bieber like I my example last
time you were on you know someone you
know that's richer or more powerful
because I'm sure that you know a lot of
guys will come in your life and try to
you know and they don't care whether you
have a boyfriend or not they're still
going to try to pursue you so you have
to you know you have to be in that situ
you have to like as a man you'd have to
be really really really
secure yeah I would say that he
definitely is he's very very secure he
has his moments where he acts a little
crazy but I think we all do yeah I'm
sure and you have a crazy lifestyle so
when it when it came to like how are you
growing up like how like as a kid um I'm
sure because you're really talented and
I and I think you're intelligent you
know I I think that you you're you're
highly
intelligent uh how how how were you
treated as a kid in in school that's
interesting I was a I was a nerd I was a
geek um I didn't have a whole lot of
friends um when I took ballet there was
a point where I had to leave ballet and
I'm not really sure why and it was at
that point like I just changed as a
person um I ended up getting into a
friend ship that just probably wasn't
the best friendship for me at that time
um we are no longer friends I really
appreciate this person and she was
really really close to me but we made
wrong decisions together and we got
ourselves into some trouble here and
there so I think I was I was almost like
retaliating against my parents for
attention right and then by High School
um I gotten into so much trouble that I
think that kid didn't really want to be
my friend so I started hanging out with
band and
choir kids and that was when I I decided
like hey I I should focus on like my
artistic abilities because I I have a
bit of talent and it's going to keep me
out of trouble so I did that and then I
mean After High School I lost my father
got into more trouble I mean my life has
been quite an interesting story and
that's why I'm going to write a book I
have been writing the book and um how
everything just kind of came together
for my life and that kind of stuff but
um for the most part I was picked on and
teased um there were days I ate I ate my
lunch in the bathroom to avoid
people um whoa that's crazy yeah I
remember a girl uh throwing apples at me
and I get picked on I still have some of
my high school bullies still picking on
me they still roast me online but now at
this point now I kind of look at it as
you're still like this like you haven't
moved on you haven't grown up you
haven't done anything you're still
picking on me okay I'm flattered yeah
you know when I was on YouTube um I used
to get the nword a lot and you know I
got a lot of VD like a lot of hits and
stuff like that and and I realized that
you know when you when they made me
partner and I started making money off
every every video I was like hate on
hate on give me the hate you know
because the hate kind of gave me uh you
know it made me a lot of money you know
for just Lage schol honestly like I mean
for the people that I don't really like
I don't really have an opinion
on like it's not even that I don't like
you it's just like I don't have an
opinion on you're you're living your own
life you're having your own lifestyle
you're doing what you do I don't even
know what your job is and that's how
much I know about you but for me it's a
little bit different when they hate on
me it's because they see me doing things
they see me making moves and they want
to say something and I don't know I I
just let them do that at this point
there are times where I get involved on
line and I
start being Saucy back
but um I think I do that for reader
interest yeah keep keep things spicy I
don't take it too seriously anymore
people think that I do but I really
don't yeah for sure okay well I'm going
to just cut we're going to cut to just a
quick uh clip here and then we'll be
back um in about 2 minutes or so or less
than that so anyway uh so we're just
going to put this uh we'll be right back
everyone oh well you made your bed okay
we are live so um again welcome to the
hustle Zone uh and if you guys ever if
you're an entrepreneur and you want to
provide content to the to to the hustle
Zone like kind of like those clips that
you've seen uh just make sure to uh
message me and do with a one minute
video of your oneliner not oneliner but
your your nugget and we will uh
definitely put it up there um like I
said all the links are in the
description above like if you want to
support us um you know uh and we we will
take any donation uh we'll also take um
you know or you can you can purchase one
of these guys uh hustle own sweater
hustle own shirt uh and then for the
ladies we got tank tops uh uh white and
black and they're nice they got glitter
on it I when I first got the shirts I
was like what's this shirt I put it on
and I'm like looks kind kind like I
don't know why you sent me like a you
know like it was like a like a shirt
like I don't know what what you'd call
it like a woman's shirt so it was like
with glitter and stuff like that and I'm
like oh this is for the ladies so uh
make sure to um if please support us so
that we can continue doing this and
providing this sort of content because
you know and why do you want to do this
because we are a group that wants to
highlight entrepreneurialism as a
culture we want to tell the stories we
want to normalize entrepreneurial ISM
because there's a lot of people that
just misunderstand us and we just want
our voice heard but we want it done in a
nice way uh and we put a lot of quality
in our broadcast we put a lot of quality
in the things that we write we put a lot
of quality in the website and all that
stuff that we're developing um but in
order to put that quality in we need the
support so if you can kindly click those
links send us a donation even $5 $2 $1
um or purchase one of the the sweaters
uh that would be greatly appreciated uh
so um we're going to get back to our
guest here so so yeah so now what does
it take to be you what does it take to
be me yeah I think you have to be bat
[ __ ] you have to be B hold on a
second okay I just got to like cut to
myself for a
second
um you have to be bat [ __ ] like did you
say bat like as in like Batman batom
[ __ ] yeah like bats like the flying
rodents okay because I was like
what what she talking about that's what
I instead of saying you're crazy I say
you're bat
[ __ ] so tell me expound upon that please
um well I think you have to be crazy to
like go full force into your dreams this
much and like believe in yourself this
much and be this driven like I I don't
know I don't know where I get this
motivation from but I think it's kind of
from the hardships that I've been
through and the hardships made me crazy
like they made me insane at some points
in my life but I mean it gave me a sort
of new sense of light of like what it is
I want to conquer and what it is I want
to
achieve um and I mean the craziness the
being the bad [ __ ] only only made me
more motivated like hey like I have to
be driven I have to believe in this I
don't have a choice at this point like
some people are okay with uh doing their
nine-to-five job and I just was not okay
doing that I was never okay I I was
always getting lost in my life over and
over again and I just didn't understand
why and it was because I was
unhappy and then suddenly when I started
doing this um I I noticed that people
started gravitating towards me more as a
person they they were more intrigued
they were more interested in who I am
and where I'm going and it's only
because I believed in me so much that
others started believing in me too so I
mean I think you have to be some level
of B [ __ ] to think that you're so
special that something good could happen
to you but I'm happy that I'm I'm not
crazy to think that that was me in my
life right
now I usually when women come on I asked
this
question uh
because this is just something we need
to kind of get rid of this myth that you
know entrepreneurs get it easy the first
thing that people are going to say it's
like well she's a model and she's pretty
she probably has guys all over the place
that want to give her cars and money and
this and that
um you know she has it easy so
um tell me tell me do you have it easy
because of your
looks no I definitely didn't I was never
taken really that all that
seriously um and I think I said a lot of
times when I'm in a room full of men I'm
still not taken seriously I've been told
even just recently be quiet little girl
like I'm not supposed to have an opinion
or something and that gives me a level
of fury like because I'm just trying to
make it as a business woman I want to be
taken seriously I want to I want to do
everything it is I can to have this
career that I Inspire to have and like I
am a driven person there's no way that I
could have gone from being an abused
Homeless girl who had I was a drunk too
like I had
issues to going to this now without
being a driven motivated person and like
so to say that girls have it easy well I
also as a woman had it hard where I was
being beat because I was a woman you
know I wasn't supposed to talk
back and for that I was homeless because
I wanted to run away from that so I I
don't think it's fair to say
that women have it easier to become an
entrepreneur because we certainly do not
I it's so hard for me to want to express
like where it is I'm going and who who
it is that I think that I am without a
man coming in and saying this is who you
are sit down be quiet right now the
other thing the other obvious thing that
I can point out is that you're short you
know models are usually tall so how are
you making it as a model and you know
doing what you do in an industry that
you know is quite
subjective well I'm just really really
lucky that someone's always capturing
the right angle so I don't look like the
[ __ ] that I
actually like uh My Bodyguard 6'4 he's
huge and like honestly it was just the
other day I realized how short I was I
was wearing my flat shoes for once in my
life and he was standing next to me and
I looked at my reflection in a window
that we passed and I was like holy
crap I am so short but um I think it's
because I do a lot of like self
promotion I don't Focus too much on
trying to get into a brand brand because
I feel like I am my brand and I'm just
going to stick with that whether whether
people like it or not like that's that's
what I'm looking at doing and so far
it's worked for me in a lot of ways like
I'm getting sent free products I'm
getting free stuff I get discount stuff
just for giving them like a shout out
here and there and I mean because I
believed in myself and I said this is
what I want this is who I am and I
demanded that and only that I think
people were like oh okay I see yeah you
know and I get that and I think that
it's amazing that you have a good
understanding of branding and branding
yourself um using social media and
really self-promoting you know without
it being overly done and stuff like that
you know you share a little bit you know
because I've seen your timeline and you
share intimate stuff about your life but
I think that's that kind of goes with
your brand I think you know the more
they they get to know you they don't
really look at your height or whether
you're a female or whatever you know I
think that when you are just being real
with social media and I say that all the
time once you're real with those social
media social media is real with you if
you want to be fake and you want to you
know you know not be conscious of what
you're doing um then that can pose as a
problem um what do you think about um I
I just wanted to change the the topic
here for a few seconds um Kendall Jenner
and
Pepsi uh Kendall for for all those who
don't know Kendall did a um a commercial
where she was at maybe some sort of
rally black lives matter Rally or you
know any kind of rally and you know she
gives a Pepsi to the police officer and
then magically saves the day you know
what did you how did you feel about that
being you know being in the position
that you're in right now well I think
Kendall was just doing a job and showing
up for work because when I go on set I'm
told kind of what to do and I do it I
don't when I'm handed an outfit I mean I
could quit the job and not take it but
like that's that's not money in my
pocket anymore that's gone right are are
you guys briefed are you briefed um
beforehand on what you're going to get
yourself
into well I
mean sometimes sometimes it's it's not a
whole a lot like I've had cameramen come
up and get me at weird angles that I am
not comfortable with and I will tell
them to get the F away like that's not
okay um and I've had issues with people
that way um as far as TV sets go I know
that whatever it is that I'm going to be
doing like that they give me some level
of briefing of it and I have to agree or
decline so so I've decided for myself
that at this point like I'm just kind of
trying to break it in I am open to doing
a lot at this point I'm not open to porn
I'm not open to selling
myself
but I'm open to a lot so I mean I've had
smaller outfits on on SE um right now I
try to keep my personal profiles PG-13
I've never taken a nude photo for
anybody in my life ever um and that's
because I I knew that I wanted to Brand
myself and then you know if a nude scene
came up in a movie or TV show and I was
an option for them maybe I'd take it I
can't say that right now but I think
Kendall was just showing up for work and
doing her job and all she was doing was
handing a can of soda it's not
like I think that's probably the most of
what she got and was told that day
because they don't film the whole thing
together they don't get all those people
in that room with Kendall right like
Kendall's too hot for that you know like
she's too much of a public figure that
they wouldn't do that even like the sets
that I go on now they they rarely ever
bring the star of the show into the same
set that I'm filming whatever scene it
is that I'm in so that they have as much
privacy as possible so it's likely
Kendall didn't know who what the content
they probably I don't know I can't speak
that she definitely knew she was handing
a can of soda in a riot but I think she
bet she was just handing a can of soda
to a police officer out of good Goodwill
and it's funny because the stocks on
Pepsi went up when they aired it and as
soon as peps Pepi took it down and
released their apology stocks vomited
wow yeah the stock I I watched the stock
market at that time Pepsi's stock went
up when the when the commercial was
playing and airing and then it went down
real fast when they they admitted fault
I don't know if it was like a bad thing
or a good thing of that commercial but I
think
like I don't think that you should cower
over that way when like that's what you
wrote maybe it was bad writing but do do
you understand the implications of you
know why people would be upset with the
commercial and would absolutely but
people can get upset about everything
right and would would you have done the
commercial yourself like would you have
um
um knowing that do it differ and I'd
give everyone a count of Pepsi you know
maybe that would make the difference in
that commercial you know everybody had a
Pepsi you know what like you know you
know I can that small little little
difference maybe could have made a
difference to the commercial if if if it
wasn't just them handing a Pepsi to one
officer it' be like everyone gets a
Pepsi and then everybody's happy maybe
maybe that would be like the small right
that would change
it okay well you know what I this
probably one of the best responses that
I've heard um thus far uh so we we'll
get off get off that time topic we're
going to cut to another clip uh so we'll
be back in about a minute so I'll be
[Music]
back we must always ask ourselves this
one question to be able to bring forth
growth and expansion and change in our
operation and that one question is this
what can I be able to do better more or
different we should be able to
comfortably and confidently ask this
question to the people that we are
leading in our lives and around us and
organizations wherever it
is the reality is is that by definition
insanity is doing the same thing over
and over again and expecting a different
result and we know this sad thing is is
that a lot of people are going through
that and they're beating their head
against the wall and wondering why
nothing will change I challenge you ask
this question to yourself what can I do
better more or
different e
you probably couldn't hear me because my
mic was on mute but hey I am back uh
we're almost done with the set we're
going to we're going to we're going to
go through our last line of questioning
uh uh folks I would not be here again
without you all so thank you guys all
for participating uh please take the
time if you guys have found value in
this please share this again like it
again um you know so that we can we can
get this message out to as many
entrepreneurs as possible uh that is our
goal and and in to help us do this
full-time and to do this more often and
to provide you with even better quality
uh you know purchase the hustle own
shirt you know and the sweater and and
the gear or donate so links are in the
description uh and uh and we we're going
to get back to our guest here so Janine
so how are you liking the the hustle on
so far I love it so I watch it a lot I
think you can see
that well yeah you know and I was like
you know I was going to ask you to be a
part of it a long time ago but you know
I was just you know just so much happens
on on a given day that it's hard for me
to keep track but anyway thank you for
having me as a guest I I love getting to
share my story um I mean like if it
weren't for my story I wouldn't be where
I am and I feel like I can do a lot
change other people's situations and
their
own uh way of thinking with the way I
thought like I mean you you never know
what you can do with your life you never
know what whose lives you could affect
and change and I had people change mind
for the better and ever since that I've
been a very charitable person and very
giving person and I think that um a lot
of more women need to hear my story a
little bit because there's a lot of
women out there who are not getting out
of those bad relationships not doing
what they can to get somewhere better
and I think I'm living proof that there
is better yeah yeah I think so too I not
to chew my own horn too too much well
you know you're you're self-aware and I
think that's amazing
um and I think that you know I think
that most women your age are not that
self-aware I don't know do people say
that you have a um an old soul because
you seem to have one I do do I always
got that see when I was a kid growing up
um people would ask me what my favorite
song is and I would say Revolution and
they would say by who and I say The
Beatles and they'd be like what like ew
why like you listen to old people
music
and I don't know I the song Revolution
is about change in the world and the
change that John lenon wished to see in
the world and he Furious about how
there's no change and that's that's me
in a nutshell like I'm always sitting
there like thinking like what what can I
do to change not just my world but the
world for other people yeah I got told I
have an old soul from a very very young
age that's amazing and just you what you
were saying is like serving people I
think that's the nucleus of being an
entrepreneur is like you know realizing
that you have the ability to change the
world you know you wouldn't be able to
be an entrepreneur if you didn't believe
that you could change the world and you
know and when you pursue in helping the
world and trying to change things you
know you you you affect so many people
you know and if you do good job then
they pay for you they make sure that you
have a nice hotel room that you have
luxury things so we're going to get into
the last lineing questioning here so um
Janine what's your favorite um what's
your favorite drink
um it's a
oldfashioned an
oldfashioned even your beverage is
old everyone's like why do you drink an
old man's drink too yeah that's pretty
classy I'm either drinking an
oldfashioned or I'm drinking Jin wow
okay uh what's your favorite your
favorite
dessert uh
cheesecake I love cheesecake or green
tea ice cream ew
E green tea ice cream that has such a I
eat so much Asian food uh that's another
thing about me I I date a lot of Asian
boys so you have a lot of uh and what
would be your favorite uh Asian dish
then oh I don't know I really like hot
pot um which is Korean like kimchi
soup that they put a bunch of mixed
meats or Seafoods into a pot with Ramen
and it's flavored with really spicy
kimchi sauce and I like that a lot
that's one of my favorite foods um I
Love
Sushi um I don't know I I just love
Seafood I'm really open-minded with food
there's only two Foods I'd never tried
and and and what are those Foods Sauer
cat which is funny because I'm
German and that's only because my dad or
my mom used to make it in my house as a
kid and I don't know if you've ever
smelt cabbage fermenting for sauerkraut
but it is the nastiest smell in the
world yeah no I hate sauerkraut I'm just
like that's yeah the second is
watermelon and watermelon you haven't
had tried watermelon I haven't had
watermelon since I was a kid I I hate
watermelon flavored candies water
flavored ice cream sorbet
anything watermelon including watermelon
itself I hate it it's gross it makes me
gag yeah same with me and sea you like
seafood and I hate Seafood I haven't
tried well I'm allergic to fish and then
I just don't eat seafood or anything
that it's not a you know not a bird or a
cow you know so um what makes you
mad what makes me mad when I feel like
I'm not being listened to that's
probably like the thing that makes me
the most mad cuz I will just talk over
top of you if you're not going to listen
to me and then and then we've got a
screaming
B what is
your what is your philosophy for
life
um that's a great question i' probably
say it has to be the one that's tattooed
on my arm it um oh here oh I can't see I
can't see it oh it's not tilting the
right
way and what is that what does that read
it says with every mistake we must
surely be
learning and why would you choose
something like that it's from While My
Guitar Gently Weeps By The Beatles
oh and I've made a lot of mistakes in my
life and for that I can't be angry at
myself because I learned from
them do you believe that you you know
have you m made the same mistake twice
oh
absolutely
and like fool me once shame on you fool
me twice I'm the fool right right right
so if I if I do the same thing twice
I've only kicked myself sometimes I've
done it four times like you know but I
you know I would suggest other people
when you make a mistake not to do it
over and over and over again because at
that Point you're just I what what is it
they say about mental health issues it's
like you're your psycho if you make the
same mistake over and over and over and
over right the definition of insanity
expecting a different yeah expecting a
different assault yeah that's the
definition of insanity and I I have done
it but I mean that's not the path that
I'm on anymore I've definitely learned
from a lot of my
mistakes Michael Jackson or Prince I I
this is my favorite question because
Jackson oh my gosh I got a Michael
Jackson in my suitc shirt right here
what I'm a Michael Jackson fan that's
something about me is that I colle
collect uh banded t-shirts and I found a
vintage store here in Vancouver that was
just ridiculous and I I think I bought
six or seven shirts I feel like I really
want to show you guys yes please show us
if I can find it I'm this suitcase is
such a mess right
now oh there it
is oh what Michael Jackson straight up
you got you got some hustle Zone points
for
that awesome and um are you a neat
person or you a messy person I'm a bit
of both it honestly depends on my mood I
get super super obsessive compulsive
when I'm stoned and that's something
that I I I do and I'm okay with sharing
that with people because I have a
prescription for it and I think that
alternative medicine is a beautiful
medicine we're going to have to talk
about that another time because uh yeah
we'll do another issue all about yeah
all about that because I think that we
can great debate about it yes a great
debate that's a good debate great debate
uh subject um you know what actually
yeah we'll have to do that um we'll have
to do we'll have to talk offline and
yeah I get super OCD when I'm smoking um
but if I'm in a bad mood like let's say
I'm like sad someone hurt me and I'm
like crying about it then suddenly I get
like a huge
slob like it's like I could have like a
food that I ate two days ago sitting on
like next to my bed and I won't move
yeah but then you know I pick myself
back up again I clean but lately in my
life it's been super super neat and
organized I can't do anything but I'm
here with my bodyguard and he is the
biggest
slob and he didn't leave me any room for
any of my stuff which is
funny I'll tell you when I'm done okay
so
um okay so we have to wrap things up my
son is like I really want to play the
games that I got for my
birthday so I got to get going so uh
thank you so much Janine uh what did you
think about the hustle Zone thank you
for having me Ryan I'm looking forward
to coming back and talking to you again
I'm have to my own nice camera and mic
like you do yeah well you know just hit
me up I I'll give you some of the
secrets uh okay but uh yeah Janine's
going to be working with the hustle Zone
uh behind the scenes as well so um uh
when I make the big announcement you
guys will know exactly what's going on
but we you know we're working away so
again make sure you guys purchase this
because it won't be it would be
impossible for us to do what we need to
do without your support uh so Janine
thank you so much for uh attending to
this day's show uh there is a tradition
for every house Zone that I've done the
tradition is a call and response so I'm
going to say welcome to the um hustle
Zone and then you say the hustle Zone
but you got to scream it as loud as you
can oh I have to scream it okay I can do
that concerned hopefully your bodyguard
doesn't come in
like he'll be like why the [ __ ] you
screaming and folks um you know when
we're going to include the the audience
in this when we say the hustle Zone I
want you to like like like like like as
much as you can and share share share
share share as much as you can so when
she says the hustle Zone I want you to
like now if she doesn't do it well you
need to do an angry face okay and then
we'll do it again until she gets it
right so uh let's see here uh I'm going
to just take I'm going to prop up my the
image Okay so
welcome to the hustle Zone whoa my ears
yeah you were not expecting that I
wasn't here that that was good you got
you got you got pip do you sing I do
sing so can you can you sing something
cuz you know this this if you can sing
you need to you need to you need to sing
something before we
go oh I don't know I can't think of
anything to say
I don't really know just say anything
just give us give us like one bar of
something you take
the
and right
out and
[Music]
I I don't want to sing right now why I
love it so
much well you know what I put you on the
spot and I always put you on the spot
but thank you so much no I didn't even
sing the right words and then it threw
me
off so sad I just brushed that that's
okay you know what it's that yeah I I
keep on putting you on the spot but it's
you know the thing is is that what I
like about you is that you're you're you
just you come ready you know you're
ready to to perform your definition of a
true performer um and uh a true
professional and you know even some of
the the quality responses that I got
today from you uh you know I can see
that you're future there's a lot going
to be in your future in terms of your
career and you building your brand and
and stuff you know because you really
have to have a good business mindset in
order for you to go further and the fact
that you know exactly where you want to
go and you're not going to let people
get into your way I think that's amazing
so uh every everyone give give her a
like for this like thumbs up I think
this this was a great uh don't like my
singing voice though that was really bad
I haven't that was good that was good
like I you know you weren't you weren't
you weren't pitchy there was those few
parts where like cuz my audio was really
bad so I couldn't hear but you know for
the most part it was good uh
so
so uh thank you so much uh uh Janine for
for hopping in uh so folks that was a
great interview I enjoyed it
um uh there's not much I can say about
you know a lot of young women want to be
famous a lot of young women want to get
into you know the first thing they do
it's like you know even when I was a kid
I want to be famous uh and I want to be
a rapper and and whatnot I was in my 20s
and you know that was kind of why I'm
here why I've gotten to this point um
but I came about it in a roundabout way
and it's weird that I'm doing what I
love to do now I wasn't really I was
doing what I thought I loved and now I'm
doing what I love to do and it's not
even about the fame it's just about
providing people with great content and
so
I um you know I applaud I applaud Janine
to just have a really good understanding
of where she wants to go and and and and
you know like when you're when you're a
model or you're actress sometimes you
don't have a promising career but the
fact that she wants to be a
businesswoman and that she wants to
build you know and she wants to have her
hands in in different things I think
that is amazing so um I do thank her for
for coming in uh
so you guys want to add yourself to the
group and like our page because we're
going to be coming up with the the
hustle on Magazine the only way for you
to get notified right now is by adding
yourself to the group and uh to the page
so if you want to keep up with the
hustle Zone please do so I'm going to go
through the comments right now before I
leave and uh so uh uh moose says map
says uh thank you Ryan
Perez
um uh thank you Susan and uh sorry thank
you Craig Myers for
sharing
um moose says uh like the hustle
Zone uh Michael says another wonderful
presentation Ryan Perez thank you for
being uh being a guest and sharing so
very much here on the hustles on 2.0
yeah thank you um I'm like I'm liking
away thank you so much Jamie for liking
away this was amazing um it's her mic if
she can get a little closer to the mic
okay um yeah I knew that there were some
issues with the mic wasn't sure um Mark
um good good evening to you all Mark
Duncan and um thank you for for for your
your continued support uh we had Jason
Daniels in the house we had uh all kinds
of people today man we got a lot of
comments thank you guys so much and
again links are in the description um I
will talk to you later um but we I can't
leave without uh showing my credits so
we're just going to do that and Janine
is on the credits so you can add that
Janine to your
indb the hustle Zone what what what but
yeah thank you guys so much and I will
talk to you